Guide to the Sylvester Manor Archive 1649-1996 MSS.208
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Record Group IV: Horsford Family
  - Series A: Eben Norton Horsford
    - Subseries 1: Correspondence
      - Subsubseries a: Academic and Family
        - Ayraum, Walter: East Avon, NY, 1842 August 22; cuid1679 (Box 55, Folder 58)
          Addressed To: “Eben N. [Norton] Horsford, Esq., Moscow [Leicester], Livingston County, NY”
          Sent From: "Walter Ayraum"
        - Bacon, Josiah: Boston, MA, 1868 March 20; cuid1680 (Box 55, Folder 59)
          1 Letter with Indentation
          Sent From: “Treasurer Josiah Bacon, Goodyear Dental Vulcanite Company, No. 46 School Street, Boston, MA”
        - Bacon, LJ: Boston, MA, 1887 November 7; cuid1681 (Box 55, Folder 60)
          Sent From: "Clerk L.J. Bacon of the American Ballot Box Association, No. 47 Devonshire Street, Boston, MA"
          In Reference To: Business / Politics / Professional; December elections; Stockholder Meeting
          Measurements: 8” x 10.5”
        - Bacon, NA: [Albany, NY], 1843 January 4; cuid1682 (Box 55, Folder 61)
          Sent From: "N.A. Bacon," [Unidentified Location, Possibly Albany, NY]
        - Bacon, SY: Boston, MA, 1868 December 31; cuid1683 (Box 55, Folder 62)
          Sent From: “S.Y. Bacon, 1478 Washington Street, Boston," [MA]
          In Reference To: Business / Professional / Technology; “European Patents in Safes”
        - Bagshaw, John: Riverhead, NY, 1887 August 23 & 27; cuid1684 (Box 55, Folder 63)
          Sent From: “Searcher of Titles to Lands in Suffolk County, John Bagshaw - Real Estate and Insurance Agency, Riverhead, NY”
          In Reference To: Business / Professional / Real Estate; Shelter Island Rental Inquiry
          Measurements: 5.75” x 9”
        - Bain, Jr., James: Toronto, Canada, 1889 September 4 & October 5; cuid1685 (Box 55, Folder 64)
          Addressed To: “Professor [Eben Norton] Horsford, Cambridge, [MA]; "Wellesley College," [Wellesley, MA]
          Sent From: “Chief Librarian James Bain Jr., of the Toronto Public Library”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; Canadian Bibliography; "The Problem of the Northmen," Judge Daly; Professor Campbell of Montreal
        - Baker, William Emerson: Boston, MA, 1877 September 5; cuid1686 (Box 56, Folder 1)
          Addressed To: [Eben Norton Horsford, Wellesley, MA]
          Sent From: “William Emerson Baker of The 'Alice M.' Chemical Club, 13 West Street, Boston," [MA]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Professional / Science; "Analysis of Ridge Hill Farms by 'Alice M' Chemical Club, Analytical Dr. James R. Nichols, President"
          Measurements: 5.25” x 3.25”
        - Bandelin, Ad. F: Santa Fe, NM, 1887 August 21; cuid1687 (Box 56, Folder 2)
          Addressed To: "Professor," [Eben Norton Horsford]
          Sent From: "Ad. F. Bandelin"
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Native Americans / Professional; David Zeisberger's Indian Dictionary
        - Banks, Thomas G: Watertown, MA, 1889 November 26; cuid1688 (Box 56, Folder 3)
          Sent From: "Surveyor Thomas G. Banks of the Office of Surveyor of Highways," [Watertown, MA]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; "The Problem of the Northmen”
        - Barker, [Aeau SS]: Boston, MA, 1888 December 21; cuid1689 (Box 56, Folder 4)
          Sent From: "[A. Barker], Office of U.S. Light-House Inspector, Second District, Box 5343, Boston, MA”
        - Barnard, Frederick Augustus Porter: New York & Scarborough On-Hudson, NY, 1874 March 28 - December 28; 1875 February 3; 1886 January 21; cuid1690 (Box 56, Folder 5)
          Sent From: “Frederick A.P. [Augustus Porter] Barnard, Columbia College, New York / Scarborough On-Hudson, NY”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; “John Cabot’s Landfall in 1497”; Mr. Johnson’s “Flour” Article
          11 Pages, Bound & Unbound
          Frederick Augustus Porter Barnard (May 5, 1809 – April 27, 1889) was a deaf American educator and scientist. Barnard became the 10th president of Columbia College (now Columbia University) in 1864 and held the position until 1888. The Frederick Augustus Porter Barnard Papers (1831-1889) are preserved at Columbia University in New York, NY.
        - Barnard, MP: Stratham, MA, 1890 February 9; cuid1691 (Box 56, Folder 6)
          Sent From: “M.P. Barnard, No. 2 Bernis Avenue, Stratham, MA”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional / Science; Basin of the Charles; Norumbega; Parker Memorial Science Class; Tower at Stony Brook
        - Barnum, George G: Buffalo, NY, 1889 July 10; 1890 October 18; cuid1692 (Box 56, Folder 7)
          Sent From: “Corresponding Secretary George G. Barnum, The Buffalo Historical Society, Buffalo Library Building, Buffalo, NY”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; Leif Erikson [Ericson] Statue, “Monument to Red Jacket”; “The Problem of the Northmen”
        - Barnum, Herman N: Auburndale, MA, 1887 June 6, September 6 & October 12; cuid1693 (Box 56, Folder 8)
          2 Letters, 1 United States Postal Card with Postage
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, 27 Craigie Street, Cambridge, MA”
          Sent From: "Herman N. Barnum"
          In Reference To: Friendship / Personal / Social; Phil Parsons
          Measurements: 5” x 3” - 5” x 8”
        - Barnum, PT (Phineas Taylor): Bridgeport, CT, 1878 April 19; cuid1694 (Box 56, Folder 9)
          Sent From: "P.T. [Phineas Taylor] Barnum"
          In Reference To: Business / Professional; Frances C. White
          Phineas Taylor Barnum (July 5, 1810 – April 7, 1891) was an American businessman and showman remembered for promoting celebrated hoaxes and for founding the Barnum & Bailey Circus. The Phineas Taylor Barnum Papers (1818-2000) are preserved at Tufts University in Medford / Somerville, near Boston, MA.
        - Barrons, John Manning: Olivet, MI, 1887 June 31 & July 11; cuid1695 (Box 56, Folder 10)
          2 Letters with Indentation
          Addressed To: "My Dear Old Friend," [Eben Norton Horsford]
          Sent From: "John Manning Barrons"
          In Reference To: Friendship / Personal / Religion / Social; Edward Fuller; "Reverend Leroy Warren, Superintendent of the Congregational Churches of Michigan"
        - Barrows, Marion EH: Union, NH, 1889 July 26; cuid1696 (Box 56, Folder 11)
          Sent From: "Marion E.H. Barrows"
          In Reference To: Friendship / Personal / Poetry / Social; “Birthday Greeting” Poem
        - Barrows, Reverend W: Cataumet, MA, 1889 August 4; cuid1697 (Box 56, Folder 12)
          Sent From: “Reverend W. Barrows, D.D. Agent of Whitman College, Washington Territory, [Reading, MA] with Reverend John A. Hamilton, D.D. Secretary, American College and Education Society, 10 Congregational House, Boston," [MA]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; "The Problem of the Northmen"
          Measurements: 5.75” x 8.75”
        - Barry, Ephraim L: Waltham, MA, 1889 October 5; cuid1698 (Box 56, Folder 13)
          Sent From: “Ephraim L. Barry, Printer, Music Hall Avenue, Waltham, MA”
          Printed Handwritten in Ink
        - [Bartersh], Johann: Berlin, Germany, 1883 November 22; cuid1699 (Box 56, Folder 14)
          Sent From: "Johann [Bartersh]"
          In Reference To: Business / Professional; G.A. Fiske; In German Language
        - Bartlett, John: Cambridge, MA, 1881 January 18; 1889 October 4; cuid1700 (Box 56, Folder 15)
          Addressed To: “Mr. [Eben Norton] Horsford”
          Sent From: “John Bartlett, 165 Brattle Street, Cambridge," [MA]
        - Batchelder, John M: Cambridge, MA, 1889 June 17; cuid1701 (Box 56, Folder 16)
          Sent From: "John M. Batchelder"
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; Brattle Street to Charles River, “Windmill Hill”
        - Bateman, CH: Shelter Island Heights, NY, 1889 August 30 & September 8; cuid1702 (Box 56, Folder 17)
          2 Letters with Indentations
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Shelter Island, NY”
          Sent From: "C.H. Bateman"
          In Reference To: Business / Professional / Travel; American Southwest, Arizona, Texas, Mexico
        - Bates, Charlotte Fiske: [Cambridge, MA], 1886 December 18; cuid1703 (Box 56, Folder 18)
          Sent From: "Charlotte Fiske Bates"
          Charlotte Fiske Bates (Mme. Rogé) (November 30, 1838 – September 1, 1916) was an American writer. Bates published "Risks and Other Poems" (1879) which includes 120 poems, ten sonnets, ten French translations (which were originally done for Longfellow's Poems of Places), and five epithalamia. Bates also contributed many articles to magazines, and edited the Longfellow Birthday Book (1881), Seven Voices of Sympathy(1881), and the Cambridge Book of Poetry and Song(1882). Much of Bates' work is available through New York University Libraries via BobCat.
        - Baxter, James Phinney: Macworth Island, ME, 1889 July 3; cuid1704 (Box 56, Folder 19)
          Addressed To: “Eben Norton Horsford, Esq., Cambridge, MA”
          Sent From: "James Phinney Baxter"
          James Phinney Baxter (1831 - 1921) was an American businessman, civic leader, historian, and benefactor of Portland, Maine. Baxter's personal library of over 100 leather-bound books of maps, portraits, engravings and personal letters, is available for reference at the Portland Public Library in Portland, ME.
        - Baxter, Sylvester: Boston & Malden, MA, 1882 February 21 - 1890 July 8; cuid1705 (Box 56, Folder 20)
          15 Letters, 3 United States Letter Sheet Envelopes, 4 United States Postal Cards with Ephemera, Notation & Postage
          Addressed To: “Professor [Eben Norton] Horsford, Esq., 27 Craigie Street, Cambridge, MA,” “Shelter Island, NY”
          Sent From: "Edmund Noble of Boston, MA"; “Sylvester Baxter, The Boston Herald, 255 Washington Street, Boston, MA,” “Ledgewood Terrace, Murray Street, Malden, MA”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Professional / Travel; 1 Boston Herald Newspaper Clipping “1529 Map received at state library”; Charles E. Parsons; News from San Diego; Professor Putnam & Bjornsson; Professor Sayce; Visits to Arizona, Mexico, Providence
          32 Pages, Bound & Unbound
          Measurements: 5” x 3.25” - 7.75” x 10”
          Sylvester Baxter (1850 - 1927) was an American newspaper writer and Boston urban planner. In 1893 he became the first secretary of the Massachusetts Metropolitan Park Commission, and along with Charles Eliot, was a chief force in the development of the Metropolitan Park System of Greater Boston. Many of Baxter's published works are available through New York University Libraries via BobCat.
        - Beach, Moses Y: Lenox & Pittsfield, MA, 1890 July 11; cuid1706 (Box 56, Folder 21)
          Addressed To: “[Eben Norton] Horsford, Esq.”
          Sent From: “Editor & Proprietor, Moses Y. Beach of The Berkshire County Eagle, Job Printing & Book Binding, Established 1789, Pittsfield, MA / Lenox, MA”
        - Beale, MC: Boston, MA, 1887 April 11 - December 29; 1889 May 2; undated, circa 1887 - 1889; cuid1707 (Box 56, Folder 22)
          8 Letters with Notation, 1 Financial Record, 1 United States Postal Card with Postage
          Sent From: “M.C. Beale, Caligraph Copying, 36 Bromfield Street / 28 State Street, Boston," [MA]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; Brochure of “Landfall of John Cabot”; 1 Bill of Sale, “Copying Letters on South American Excursion”
          Typed, Printed & Handwritten in Ink & Pencil
          Measurements: 5” x 3” - 8.5” x 7”
        - Beatty, JH: New York, NY, 1887 October 31; cuid1708 (Box 56, Folder 23)
          Sent From: "J.H. Beatty, 138 West 53rd Street, New York, NY”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / History / Professional; The New York Tribune proposes publication of “The Northmen of America” / "The Problem of the Northmen"
        - Beauchamp, William Martin: Baldwinsville, NY, 1887 August 22 & September 3; cuid1709 (Box 56, Folder 24)
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Cambridge, MA / Shelter Island, NY”
          Sent From: "W.M. / William M. [Martin] Beauchamp"
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Native Americans / Professional; Indian Prayer Book of 1743; Lexicon of German & Oneidas & Onondaga Language; Library of Philadelphia; Study of the Mohawk
          Measurements: 5.25” x 3” - 5” x 8”
          William Martin Beauchamp (March 25, 1830 – 1925) was an American ethnologist and Episcopal clergyman. Beauchamp published several works on the archeology and ethnology of the Haudenosaunee (Iroquois) in New York. The William Martin Beauchamp Papers (1840-1944) are preserved at the New York State Library in Albany, NY.
        - Bell, Arthur: New York, NY, 1887 August 30; cuid1710 (Box 56, Folder 25)
          Addressed To: “E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Esq., Shelter Island, NY”
          Sent From: “Cashier Arthur Bell of the Howard Insurance Company, No. 66 Wall Street, New York, NY”
          In Reference To: Business / Professional; Bill of Premiums on Policies Purchased; "Assistant Secretary George H. Allen, President Henry A. Oakley, Vice President & Secretary Charles A. Hull"
        - Bell, Clark: New York, NY, [no year] January 7, circa 1880s; cuid1711 (Box 56, Folder 26)
          Sent From: “Law Offices of Clark Bell, 57 Broadway, New York, NY,” “Leon P. Kuhl, Publisher, 817 Broadway, New York, NY”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Professional; "Leon P. Kuhl Medical-Legal Paper Series available to subscribers"
        - Benjamin, Jack: [Norwich, CT], [no year] January 24, circa 1880s; cuid1712 (Box 56, Folder 27)
          Sent From: "Jack Benjamin"
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Professional
        - Benjamin, Marcus: New York, NY, 1887 February 3 - 18, July 13 - 18; cuid1713 (Box 56, Folder 28)
          4 Letters, 1 Biographical Information Request Form [Blank]
          Sent From: “Marcus Benjamin, Office Appletons’ Cyclopaedia of American Biography, No. 63 Bleecker Street, New York, NY,” “43 East 67th Street, New York, NY”
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Professional; Editors James Grant Wilson, Professor John Fiske, Publishers D. Appleton & Company
          Measurements: 5.25” x 8” - 7.5” x 11”
        - [Bergen, Norway], 1882 December 30; 1883 January 21; 1888 November 29 & December 1; cuid1714 (Box 56, Folder 29)
          6 Letters, 2 Calling Cards, 1 Envelope with Indentation, Notation & Postage
          Addressed To: “Professor [Eben Norton] Horsford, No. 27 Craigie Street, Cambridge, MA”
          Sent From: [Alida Fougner]; “Ingeborg Rasmussen, 443 South Leavitt Street, Waukesha / Milwaukee,” [WI]; "Thea Nicolaysen"; [Wilhelm Nielsen, Bergen, Norway]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Friendship / History / Personal / Professional / Social / Travel; German, Norse, Scandinavian Inquiries; Professor Farrar; [Pressed Norwegian Plants]
          26 Pages, Bound & Unbound
          Measurements: 3.5" x 2" - 8" x 10"
        - [Berker, Valustrin]: New York, NY, 1863 October 28; 1864 January 21; cuid1715 (Box 56, Folder 30)
          Addressed To: “E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Esq.”
          Sent From: [Valustrin Berker]
          In Reference To: Business / Professional / Science / Technology; Patents
        - Biddle, Emily M: Philadelphia, PA, [no year] June 24, circa 1880s; cuid1716 (Box 56, Folder 31)
          Sent From: “Emily M. Biddle [Mc Biddle], 1210 Walnut Street," [Philadelphia, PA]
          Measurements: 4” x 6”
        - Bigelow, MB with Anson Hardy & Charles Burley: Boston, MA, 1863 January 17 - 29; cuid1717 (Box 56, Folder 32)
          3 Letters, 1 American Telegraph Form
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Smithsonian Institute, Washington D.C.”
          Sent From: “Patent Agent Anson Hardy, Treasurer Charles Burley & Manufacturer M.B. Bigelow, 32 School Street, Boston, MA”
          In Reference To: Business / Professional / Science; Governor Bontwell, Mr. Baldwin; Mr. Durant, Mr. Pollack
          Measurements: 5.5” x 8.5” - 7.75” x 9.5”
        - Bisbee, MD: Hanover, NH, 1889 August 1; cuid1718 (Box 56, Folder 33)
          Addressed To: “Mr. Eben Norton Horsford, Cambridge, MA”
          Sent From: “M.D. Bisbee, The Trustees of Dartmouth College, Hanover," [NH]
        - Bissell, Lucy A: Shelter Island, NY, 1887 September 1; 1889 January 14 & 16; cuid1719 (Box 56, Folder 34)
          Sent From: “(Mrs. A.P.) Lucy A. Bissell of Shelter Island, Suffolk County, [Long Island], NY”
          In Reference To: Business / Financial / Professional; Dr. Bissell; Mr. Preston
          Measurements: 4.5” x 3.5” - 5.25” x 8”
        - Blake, Charles F: New York, NY, 1868 December 14 & 21; cuid1720 (Box 56, Folder 35)
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Cambridge," [MA]
          Sent From: “Charles F. Blake, 8 Pine Street, New York," [NY]
        - Blake, Clarence J: Boston, MA, 1878 June 30; cuid1721 (Box 56, Folder 36)
          Sent From: “Clarence J. Blake, Hotel Berkeley, Boston," [MA]
        - Blake, Irving: Cambridge, MA, 1887 February 7; cuid1722 (Box 56, Folder 37)
          Sent From: "Irving Blake"
        - Bloomfield, Maurice: Baltimore, MD, 1887 May 2; cuid1723 (Box 56, Folder 38)
          Sent From: "Maurice Bloomfield"
        - Bocher, F: Cambridge, MA, 1887 May 15; cuid1724 (Box 56, Folder 39)
          Sent From: "F. Bocher"
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Education / Professional; Wellesley College
        - Bodfish, Reverend JP: Canton, MA, 1888 January 7; 1889 January 11 & 21; cuid1725 (Box 56, Folder 40)
          Sent From: “Reverend J.P. Bodfish, Pastor of St. John’s Church, Canton, MA”
          In Reference To: Friendship / Personal / Religion / Social; Annual Meeting of the Bostonian Society; [Reverend Dr. Hofan]
        - Bolton, CE: Cleveland, OH, 1889 August 27 & 30; cuid1726 (Box 56, Folder 41)
          Addressed To: “Professor [Eben Norton] Horsford, Cambridge," [MA]
          Sent From: “C.E. Bolton of Bolton’s Realistic Travels in Europe & America, 490 Euclid Avenue, Cleveland, OH”
          In Reference To: Business / History / Professional; [Massachusetts Monument Inquiry]
          Measurements: 8.5” x 11”
        - Bolton, H. Carrington: New York, NY, 1887 October 1; cuid1727 (Box 56, Folder 42)
          Sent From: “H. Carrington Bolton, Lately Professor of Chemistry, Trinity College, Hartford, CT”
        - Booth, James Curtis: Philadelphia, PA, 1844 February 1; 1868 November 1; cuid1728 (Box 56, Folder 43)
          2 Letters with Notation, Postage & Seal
          Addressed To: “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Cambridge," [MA], “Newark, DE”
          Sent From: “James C. Booth of Booth & Garrett (Thomas H.), Laboratory for Practical and Analytical Chemistry, Chant Street, Rear of St. Stephen’s Church (Tenth Street, Below Market), Established 1836, Philadelphia," [PA]
          In Reference To: Academic / Business / Chemistry / Education / Professional / Science; Copy of Doremus Testimony; [Education & research of Superphosphate used in agriculture]; Mr. Boyle, Professor Friedrich Wöhler, Gottingen, [Gielsen] with Liebig, Berlin [Germany] with Professor Gustav Magnus, Rose & Mitscherlich
          James Curtis Booth (July 28, 1810 – March 21, 1888) was an American chemist who was the melter and refiner at the U.S. Mint in Philadelphia for many years. Booth was born in Philadelphia, was educated at the Hartsville Seminary, graduated from the University of Pennsylvania in 1829, and later studied at the Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute in Troy, New York from 1831 to 1832. He visited Germany between 1833 and 1835, spending the year of 1833 in Professor Friedrich Wöhler's private laboratory in Hesse-Cassel, and then spending nine months in the laboratory of Professor Gustav Magnus in Berlin. He opened a chemistry laboratory in Pennsylvania in 1836 for teaching purposes, and when the demand for teaching and chemical analysis increased, he was assisted by Dr. Martin Hans Boyè until 1845. From 1848, Thomas H. Garrett was his associate, and in 1881 the firm became "Booth, Garrett and Blair." The James Curtis Booth Papers (1785-1944) are preserved at the Othmer Library of Chemical History, Chemical Heritage Foundation in Philadelphia, PA.
        - Borden, A: New Bedford, MA, 1884 March 15; cuid1729 (Box 56, Folder 44)
          2 Western Union Telegraph Forms
          Sent From: "A. Borden"
          In Reference To: Business / Personal / Professional; Death of Mrs. Wellson; South Framingham, MA
          Measurements: 8” x 5”
        - Borden [Jr.], Gail: New York, NY & Winsted, CT, 1863 October 31; 1864 May 27 - November 17; 1865 February 22 & March 6; cuid1730 (Box 56, Folder 45)
          7 Letters with Ephemera & Indentation
          Addressed To: "Gail Borden, Esq."; “Professor E.N. [Eben Norton] Horsford, Harvard University, Cambridge, MA,” “Professor [of] Chemistry, Washington, D.C.”
          Sent From: “Professor Horsford”; “Gail Borden, Inventor, Brewster’s, Putnam County, NY,” “Office Borden Condensed Milk Company, Brewsters, South East, NY” & “Winsted, CT”
          In Reference To: Business / Chemistry / Food / Politics / Professional / Science; "36-38 Park Row, New York Belting & Parking Company"; Advertisement Clippings for “Borden’s Apple Jelly, or Concentrated Apple Juice” & “Borden’s Concentrated Animal Juices by Gail Borden & John H. Currie, for sale by NY Condensed Milk Co., 34 & 36 Elizabeth Street, New York," [NY]; Advertisement “Abraham Lincoln, for President, Andrew Johnson, for Vice-President”; Animal Food & Beef Extracts, Meat Biscuits & Tea
          Measurements: 5” x 7.75” - 7.75” x 9.75”
          Gail Borden, Jr. (November 9, 1801 – January 11, 1874), was a native New Yorker who settled in Texas in 1829, where he worked as a land surveyor, newspaper publisher, and inventor. Borden is most known as the developer of condensed milk in 1853; demand was high for his product by the Union Army during the American Civil War. The Gail Borden Papers (1830-1956) are preserved at the Daughters of the Republic of Texas Library in San Antonio, TX.
        - Borden, Richard P: Cambridge, MA, 1890 May 5; cuid1731 (Box 56, Folder 46)
          Sent From: "Richard P. Borden, 729 Cambridge Street, Cambridge," [MA]
          In Reference To: Friendship / Personal / Social; Miss Borden ℅ Baring Brothers, London, England
          Measurements: 4.5” x 6.75”
        - Boston North End Mission: Boston, MA, 1887 April 27; 1889 January & February 8; cuid1732 (Box 56, Folder 47)
          2 Letters, 1 Postcard with Board of Directors List
          Sent From: "Chairman Finance Committee, Ezra Farnsworth & Treasurer H.E. Abbott"
          In Reference To: Business / Financial / Professional; “An Emergency in City Mission Work”; “Extracts from the Annual Report, Chapel Department”
          Measurements: 5” x 3” - 6" x 9.5"
        - Boston Ornamental Iron Works, Bubier & Company: Boston, MA, 1887 November 15 - December 23; cuid1733 (Box 56, Folder 48)
          Sent From: "Bubier of Bubier & Company, Boston Ornamental Iron Works, No. 23 Exchange Street, Works 63 Merrimac Street, Boston," [MA]